{"data":[{"question":"We were both afraid because _______ us could swim.","a":"either of","b":"neither of","c":"both of","d":"neither","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Neither:  used when mentioning two things that are not true or possible","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"_________ his parents speaks English.","a":"None of","b":"Either of","c":"Neither of","d":"None","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Neither: used when mentioning two things that are not true or possible","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I have read _______ of these two books.","a":"neither","b":"either","c":"nor","d":"every","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Neither: used when mentioning two things that are not true or possible","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I saw the two programmes, but _______ was interesting.","a":"neither","b":"none","c":"either","d":"both","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Neither: used when mentioning two things that are not true or possible","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Several methods were proposed but _______ them was appropriate.","a":"neither of","b":"none","c":"neither","d":"none of","answer":"4","explain":"\n- None of: not any amount of something or not one of a group of people or things ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She _______ wrote a letter _______ gave us a ring.","a":"neither\/nor","b":"either\/or","c":"neither\/or","d":"either\/nor","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Neither ... nor ...:  used when mentioning two things that are not true or possible","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Bob and I had drunk a lot of water, so _______ us was thirsty.","a":"both of","b":"both","c":"neither of","d":"either of","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Neither : used when mentioning two things that are not true or possible ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I could see ________ the boy ________ the ball.","a":"neither\/nor","b":"either\/or","c":"both\/nor","d":"either\/nor","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Neither ... nor ...: used when mentioning two things that are not true or possible ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"_________ you and your brother are welcome.","a":"Neither","b":"Either","c":"None","d":"Both","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Both...and...: used to emphasize that something is true not just of one person, thing, or situation but also of another","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"_______ windows were wide open.","a":"Neither","b":"Both","c":"Either","d":"None","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Both: used to talk about two people, things... together","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}